The End
When you've got to play smart
Imagine if the chance the wise will take it all
Every I've seen the hell is that you're gone
So I can't be good, that I'm gone
It's going to be a universe of thoughts
I don't know if I can't, don't move
You're right, when all is done
You're right, it's gonna break
I've already seen the time
We're shotting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,決勝とした光を
今こそ解放する
We're shotting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,決戦闘 栄光のそう
核心と運命を始めよう
Well, I can hardly believe Master said that we should go out and have some fun for once
Yeah, I was super surprised
Let's hit the casino, you guys
Not just yet
The casino was a nighttime spot
Besides, we should save the main course till after the snack joins us
So what now?
We've got to get you guys looking fresh and the first step is ditching those filthy outfits
But this is the only thing I have to wear
Ain't nothing money can't fix
Yeah?
Really?
Come on!
It's time for some breakdown therapy!
Alright!
This is so cute!
Although, I'm kind of feeling this one too
Hey, look!
Cool other jacket, huh?
I spy a bathing suit section
Lots of pool parties here?
The beach is pretty far
The hot springs are close
Really?
They're a big attraction in Orphe
Especially the mixed male and female bathing pools
Yeah?
Yeah
Which means saying I can share a hot bath together!
Oh man, I think my brain really is turning into jelly
Hey, Rista, you feeling okay?
Yeah!
Just checking out these bathing suits
Pick out some for the hot springs
You mean it?
Sounds fun!
Hmm, things are all so tacky
I guess I've gotten spoiled by the high fashion options we have in the divine realm
Well, this is more of a sword and sorcery type world
So, I'll just grab the best option
She definitely heard that
This little two pieces in your size
I think it's gonna look unbelievably cute on you
Oh, thank you!
It's totes adorbs!
I suppose it could be worse
When you look around, it seems like they may actually be trying
I think this one will suit you perfectly, miss
Well, it's nice
Where's the top?
Nowhere
This is a topless model for the girl who wants to let it all hang out
I'm sure it looks simply wonderful on you
She did overhear me earlier
And now she's trying to make me look like a complete idiot
This doesn't qualify as a bathing suit!
It doesn't even cover the boobs!
Just a little much for you, huh?
It does take a certain type
What do you think of this?
Our new single-breasted model
It's just perfect
I'm not some trollop, I'm classy!
I'm sorry, but it's the new style
Just try to think of it like wearing an eyepatch when you've actually got two good eyes
It's simply a fun, carefree little piece
It's a far cry from a cosplay eyepatch lady!
Have you ever actually seen anybody just chilling with one of their girls hanging out?
Calm down, Rista
Surely a goddess can handle a little swimsuit shopping
Yeah, but all this chick is showing me is the crazy super breezy type stuff
If these aren't your style, I have bottomless suits and stuff
Want to try one?
If you're suggesting suits without a top or a bottom, why not just say go nude?
I'll find one on my own, thank you
And Mosh, do you mind grabbing one for Seiya?
Oh, sorry to pry, but does this Seiya person happen to be your boyfriend by any chance?
Damn right he is
Rista, that's not true
Then you might want this
It's a brand new, open front concept that some find flattering
Hard pass
I'll take it!
Say what?
Seiya's new elephant, but I'd sure love to see that trunk
I'll take one of these too, matey
Yeah, I can slip into this on a long steamy night
I don't get it
Quiet night
It's best if you kids don't think about it too hard
I was completely hammered off my ass when I sewed those two
I never thought anyone would actually buy them
I guess I was wrong
In honor of your daring fashion choices
You get a great deal
Thanks, sister
Great stuff at unbelievable prices
The food looks so good
I'm so hungry
Hey, how much longer till we're supposed to meet up with Master?
Oh, he said that we won't see him until later on tonight
So I guess we'll have to wait for him at the castle
Let's pig out in our room till he shows up and then we'll hit the casino
Oh yeah!
Hey!
Look alive, soldier!
So after the casino, we'll stop by the bar, get a little loose, and then it's time for the hot spring
Oh, but the Rugrats to bed, so Sai and I can have a little fun
Who cares?
If Valkyrie can do it, so can I
Theia!
Hey!
You ready?
Let's party!
Uh...
Guess he's still out running errands
But it's gonna be dark pretty soon
It was pretty clear
He did say sundown and he's not really the type to be late
Well, maybe he's having a hard time picking something else
He is a perfectionist, you know
Oh yeah, he sure is
An hour went by, and then another
We waited patiently, but our hero did not return
You haven't seen him?!
Oh, that guy with you earlier?
I haven't seen him since you got creamed by my medicinal herbs
Don't bring that up!
But Saiya told us he was gonna get some stuff to synthesize
Maybe he went to someone else's shop
Hey, are there many other item or weapon shops in town?
Yeah, I can think of a few of them
Have I seen a handsome man?
Sad to say I haven't
Nobody like that in my shop
I haven't had a single customer!
Doesn't look like he's been back here yet
And nobody in the castle has seen him either
I have no idea where he could've gone
Hey, Rista, you don't think he went to fight the demon lord alone, do you?
Huh?
No, Saiya wouldn't do that
It's completely the opposite of something he would do
He barely got through that war master fight alive
And he needed time to think
You mentioned something about training too
And the demon lord has that scary chain destruction thing
So if Saiya loses, he's dead
I'll bet he's just over-preparing since he's overly cautious
If he's training, where's he doing that?
No clue
I just don't know
I didn't want to do this, but here goes
Hello?
Huh?
Arya, what are you doing here?
Where is Ishtar?
Saiya's run off somewhere and I need to find him ASAP
What's wrong?
Come with me
Ishtar is expecting us
This is the room where time stands still
Rista, I'm so glad to see you
And your two young dragonkin friends as well
Under normal circumstances, you would be forbidden to enter this chamber
But this is an exception
Is this the place where the true souls of all the gods are kept?
Rista, I know why you've sought me out today
I'll get straight to the point
The very moment our hero left the company of your party
He headed to the demon lord's castle alone
But that doesn't seem like him
He'd never take on that fight without obsessively training first
The stakes are way too high
This chain destruction thing could destroy his soul
Not only that
Yes, such a powerful weapon could eliminate your soul as well
Saiya is very aware of that particular risk
In fact, that is precisely why he chose to go without you
Do you mean Saiya went to slay the demon lord because he was worried about me?
That can't be the reason
I mean he's always putting me down and saying things like I'm not a real goddess
He doesn't even like me
It's true he's ill-mannered and sharp-tongued
But in his heart, Saiya's a caring young man
Since he began his hero's journey
Protecting the people he truly cherishes has always been at the forefront of his mind
That's not true
No, that can't be
Seriously? He really cares about us?
Indeed
You may remember that Saiya initially resisted the two of you joining his party
But that was because he didn't want to lose any comrades
He treated you with cold detachment and always tried to keep you away from battle for the same reason
He struggled to balance his concern for your safety with his mission to protect Kayabrande
That's why he rescued you, Mosh
It's why he saved Ilulu in Dragon Village
And it's why he risked his own soul being destroyed by the War Master to get Rista out of harm's way
I still don't get it
If his main motivation has really been to protect me and the kids all along, he could have taken us back here and trained
That would be pointless, he doesn't need further training
Because the strongest goddess here has already trained him?
But couldn't he have worked to raise his level a little more?
Look, due to his extreme fake-out skill, you were never able to perceive his actual stats
But I can show you what he's been hiding
Wait a second, he's already maxed out?
Correct, he cannot progress any further
Incidentally, these are the same stats he possessed in Dragon Village
Which means his overall ratings have not increased at all since that time
It's been that long?
Feia has attempted to compensate for these stats by learning new skills such as Shining Arrow and the various Valkyriesias
This stands as more evidence of his concern
But still, he never said anything about it
Because that wouldn't change the situation
All that would lead to is unnecessary worrying
He felt there was more than enough of that already
No, he can't
He can't
With those numbers, there's no way he can beat an S-Class Demon Lord
But Master has Exaceon
If he can choose that with the Valkyriesia, he's learned
That sacred sword he has is just a fake
Say what? But he synthesized it with Elulu and Levi A's blood
The sword he got back then was not Exaceon
It was just a fake to keep you from worrying
You're kidding
His skill level has stopped rising too
He has neither the sword nor sacred armor
That's exactly why he learned Valkyrie's most advanced technique
It can strike down the enemy but the cost is one's own life
The inescapable Valkyriesia, Gate of Valhalla
No! Valkyrie told us that she would never teach him how to do that move
You witnessed their destruction aura in Vestiture ceremony, didn't you?
That's how she gave him the ability to pull off the Gate of Valhalla
Sayah's willingness to risk his life to save a world that wasn't his was enough to convince Valkyrie to trust him with her sacred Omega Valkyriesia
But if Sayah actually decides to use the Gate of Valhalla, there's no way he'll be able to survive what it's gonna do to him!
He's determined to succeed where he failed before
To protect those dear to him, and to rid himself of the specter of the past that has haunted his subconscious
To seek redemption
I don't understand. You're telling me all this stuff, and it doesn't make any sense to me
Why are we so important? And why would he need to redeem himself?
I can answer your question, but first, there is something that I must ask you
Tell me, Ristarte, do you possess a Goddess's courage to learn the truth?
Does he ever listen to a single thing we tell him? I can't deal with this!
This is how he handles everything, isn't it?
Do you actually think this is funny, cult?
Relax, Tiana. I'm sure it'll all work out in the end. It always does, right?
Whose side are you on, Arya? I just don't think we should encourage his reckless behavior
Oh, try not to let it get under your skin
Oh, Arya, is that you?
Yes, it is indeed
And what we're watching right now is the B-level mission to save a world called Exphoria
Exphoria?
Is that Seiya?
Alright guys, let's go wipe out the Chimera
Hold on, Seiya, we're not ready
The Chimera's level is way higher than ours
We should probably take some more time to train
We don't have time. Sooner we fight, sooner we win
Besides, I've got a strategy
Well, could you please share it with the rest of us?
Yeah, let's do our best
We're fine, relax
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard, that is not a strategy
We need to be 100% ready to win no matter what
It's gonna be okay, everything will work out
What? We have to take this battle seriously
Wait, Seiya, where are you going? We're not ready!
Seiya! I don't think this is a good idea
Way back then, Seiya Ryuguin was the hero I'd summoned to take control of Exphoria
What? Then why haven't I heard about this before now?
Our mage dressed in the robes was named Colt
The girl, that was Princess Tiana of Exphoria
She was our party's healer
She joined up with Seiya along the way to help defeat the demon lord
Huh?
Colt, use your wind magic!
On it! Here goes!
I'll find an opening and finish this in no time
Oh no!
Tiana, I need heals!
Okay, just hold still!
Wait Tiana, you need to heal Seiya first
He's down to his last two HP!
What? Only two?
There's a huge hole in his chest!
Oh, I'll be okay
I know this looks pretty bad, but weirdly enough it doesn't really hurt that much
I'm starting to feel like this is all just a crazy dream
You feel that way because you're about to die!
So hard to believe, he doesn't seem like the Seiya that I know at all
No, although things were looking grim, we still made it through
Look at that! We won!
You should look at us instead! We're all in horrible shape right now!
Yeah, we have been better, but it's good we beat him
You think this is good? Poor Colt had his leg ripped off!
Tiana, please hurry up and heal me!
Alright you guys, the Golem is our next target, so we better get moving
Hey, did you hear me?
Colt's gonna bloody step where his leg used to be!
So weird, are you sure that's even Master?
He reminds me of Rosalie
This is how Seiya used to behave
He hated waiting to level up, all he wanted to do was keep moving forward
He foolishly believed that his innate fighting ability would be enough
Even though his rating was low, and despite the fact that he was never prepared, he always managed to defeat the enemy, so none of us really worried all that much
Sounds to me like he was more fun then
Maybe that old Seiya actually celebrated with his friends after a victory, instead of freaking out about the next fight
We all relied on Seiya in those times, and he relied on us
Seiya, all we gotta do is beat the Demon Lord
The Demon Lord
Yeah, and we're headed out first thing tomorrow, you should make sure to get a good night's sleep
Oh, I'm way too nervous to sleep
Hey, are you sure we don't need to go to the Sage's Village?
We already have the weapon we need to win, so let's not go out of our way for anything
But we can get some information about the Demon Lord there, according to Aria
I just want to beat the Demon Lord and save the world as soon as I possibly can
You're always in such a massive hurry, aren't you?
You never make time to train or anything like that
Are you ever gonna tell me why it is you're in such a crazy rush?
It's not that complicated
No special reason
Jeez, every time I bring it up, that's all you say
This question's tomorrow, so I gotta know why
What's the real reason? Just tell me
The longer the Demon Lord is alive, the longer the people of this world will suffer
That's all there is to it
That's why we have to end this now
Okay, it's actually a good point
I would never have made it this far without your healing magic
Sorry to keep putting you out
I know that I ask a lot sometimes
It's fine, really
I'm sure things will all work out in the end
So go on and say what you always say
I always feel better after hearing it
It's gonna be okay
Everything will work out
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Way to go!
I'm just in the nick of time.
Is he dead?
The Demon Lord's HP reads zero.
It's over.
Thank goodness.
You see?
It's gonna be okay, like I told you.
I know you said that, but you really didn't have to take things down to the wire.
That was close.
My MP's at zero.
For real.
I'm a goddess and I nearly died.
Colt, no!
That's impossible.
He was dead just a second ago.
Aria, no!
I have the power of an extra life.
Take one and I'll race from the dead to have my vengeance.
This can't be happening.
If only do we consult with that sage.
You have to run away right now.
Please, go!
Goddess is a shock full of nutrients.
I feel so much better than I have in years.
Tiana, can you use your restoration magic?
No, I'm sorry.
My magic's all gone.
There's no need to apologize.
Seiya.
You were right about everything.
We should have been better prepared for this.
Run!
I think you'll make a safety law of that girl.
Stop!
Please just let her go!
No, please!
Seiya!
Hmm?
What's this?
I can sense the faintest signs of a new life coming from this woman's belly.
That's your seed growing insider, isn't it?
I think I'll have it for one last appetizer before the main course.
This mother and child will be the perfect sacrifice to usher in a new world.
Please, no!
Stop!
I beg you!
Don't do this!
No!
I believe that we've seen enough.
It wasn't Seiya's fault.
It's mine.
If only we'd gone to the sage's village and learned that secret.
As the goddess, I should have made that happen.
Hey, are you okay?
Rista!
Have the memories that once lay dormant in your soul re-emerged, Ristarte?
The poor princess whose life the hero was unable to save.
That was you, before your rebirth as a goddess of the divine realm.
Thanks to Arya's wish, as well as the good deeds Princess Tiana performed during her life, you were reincarnated as the goddess you are today.
It was no mere coincidence that you chose Seiya to bring salvation to Gaebran Day.
Fate drew your souls back together again.
Of course, as with you, Seiya has no memory of your shared past life.
But regardless, the extreme guilt and regret he felt on that day has been etched deep within his soul.
When he was once again summoned as a hero, those impressions resurfaced.
They were revealed in a single word.
What do you mean?
Do you remember when you were first getting acquainted, he used the word properties?
Properties.
Yeah, I thought he was just being difficult.
I imagine it was largely subconscious.
But this, this was the image in his mind's eye.
So that means...
Seiya is quite sharp.
And from this small passage recorded here, it seems he was aware he'd been summoned once before.
And of the tragic end he'd suffered.
I have to go.
Why would you leave right now?
Obviously, because I need to help Seiya.
Hold on, please don't go.
Rista, I can't stomach the thought of losing you again.
Although, I'm thankful for everything you've done for me.
I can't stay here.
But Rista...
I can't sit back while Seiya puts himself in harm's way.
At this point, the Demon Lord has the power to destroy gods, so I would not fault you for staying behind with us.
In fact, I recommend you do stay behind.
Seiya took measures to ensure your safety.
That was his wish.
Will you defy him?
Yeah, you're damn right I will.
This portal that you've opened leads to the Demon Lord's castle where the final battle awaits.
You realize that by entering, you overstep your role of support goddess.
I know that.
I'll face those consequences.
Rista!
Wait up!
There's no reason for you to risk your lives.
So if you really want to go back to Gaya Brande, get Ishtar to send you when this is over.
Don't be stupid!
We're going!
The only reason that we're still alive is because Seiya helped us out!
So we're gonna help him!
Really?
I realize there's no point in trying to stop you.
Yeah.
All I ask is that you be careful.
I'll do my best.
Hold on, Seiya.
I'm coming.
I'm not sure I'll be able to save you.
But I'm your friend, so I have to try.
The least I can do is not let you die alone.